### Contact

janet.pestle@allina.com

www.linkedin.com/in/janet-pestle-b9bb7244 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Hospitals
Patient Safety
Nursing

#### Certifications

Nurse Executive Board Certified NE-BC

# Janet Pestle

Vice President CNO United Hospital

Saint Paul, Minnesota

## Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Healthcare Consulting, Physician Relations, U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), Patient Safety, and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong business development professional with a DNP Candidate focused in Nursing Administration from American Sentinel University.

# Experience

Allina Health
Vice President of Patient Care, CNO
June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)
St. Paul

#### SSM Health

Vice President, Chief Nurse Executive October 2010 - April 2018 (7 years 7 months)

## Education

American Sentinel University

DNP Candidate, Nursing Administration · (2016 - 2019)

University of Missouri-Columbia BSN MSN, BSN MSN · (1989 - 1997)